STEN MAYUNGA

DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am a highly analytical and motivated individual, with extensive experience in developing dynamic web applications and software. My strength are in problem solving, communication and working on my own initiative as a self taught developer. I am passionate of my career in development and dedicated to continuous learning. I have completed numerous paid and unpaid real-world projects to showcase my competent use of front and back-end programming languages, most of which can be found on my developer website: stentechdev.com. I am a confident speaker with over a decade of public speaking experience and work very well in a team.

CONTACT

Dartford, Kent

+447861638448

stentechdev@gmail.com

stentechdev.com

linkedin.com/in/stentechdev

EDUCATION

London App Brewery

Full Stack Bootcamp

(태왕)

Visit my portfolio website:

stentechdev.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Freelance — 2014-Present

I have been designing and creating website as a hobbies and freelance web developer since 2014. I've used platform such as Wix, Shopify and Wordpress and have become familiar with Liquid and PHP as a result. My preferred programming language is JS which I am currently mastering. I am constantly learning and willing to adapt my tools according to the projects I work on.

Full Stack Developer, London App Brewery — 2021-2022

During my time studying and working on project at the London App Brewery bootcamp, I learn an extensive list of technologies and tools which includeds: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, JS ES6, DOM Manipulation, JQuery, Bash Command Line, Git, GitHub, Version Control, Node.js, NPM, Express.js, EJS, REST, APIs, Databases, SQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, Authentication, Firebase, React.js, React Hooks, Deployment with GitHub Pages, Heroic and MongoDB Atlas as well as Backend and Front-End Web Development. At the end of the bootcamp, I have completed over 25 websites.

Technical Support Specialist, Bose Corporation — 2020-2021

I worked with the US customer base by providing them with product troubleshooting and guiding customers to solve any problem that may have arisen with their Bose products or accounts. I had to learn all the products suite available and the software used to run the products. Problem solving and persistence was key in this role which had a direct correlation to customer satisfaction.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, JS ES6, DOM Manipulation, JQuery, Bash Command Line, Git, GitHub, Version Control, Node.js, NPM, Express.js, EJS, REST, APIs, Databases, SQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, Authentication, Firebase, React.js, React Hooks, Deployment with GitHub Pages, Heroic and MongoDB Atlas